rapidboards.com 2011-12-28

# Privacy Policy - RapidBoards

|  | 

Your privacy is important to us. That is why we want you to be informed about how we protect the privacy of visitors to our site. Please take a moment to read the following policy, which describes our privacy practices. 

### Collection of Information

Most of the content and services on our site are available without our collection of any personal information from you. However, in some areas of the site we may request personal information from visitors such as name, home address, e-mail address, age, interests and gender. We may collect this information when you register for a newsletter, complete a survey, purchase a product, or inquire about our services. 

In addition, some information may automatically be collected by our web servers as you browse our site. Our web server automatically collects information known as "clickstream data," such as the domain name of the service providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics. We also use cookies on our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to the hard drive of a visitor's computer for record-keeping purposes. 

### Use of Information

We use your personal information in a limited number of ways. We use the information to complete transactions, to respond to your requests, and to identify persons participating in interactive portions of our site if they are provided, such as chat rooms. We use information collected to send you e-mail updates and newsletters about our sites and to notify you if you've won a game or contest. We may share the information with our affiliates. We also may use the information you provide to send you e-mail promotions and special offers from reputable third parties in whose products and services we think you may have an interest. 

We use site generated data and cookies in the aggregate to measure the use of our site and to administer and improve our site. When we collect personal information, we may extract some of the information and combine it with other information, such as clickstream data. This combined information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this combined information is reviewed at an individual level. 

To the extent required or permitted by law, we may also collect, use and disclose personal information in connection with security-related or law enforcement investigations or in the course of cooperating with authorities or complying with legal requirements. We may also use your information as permitted by law to perform credit checks, report or collect debts owed, or protect our rights or property, our website, or its users. 

### Security

We take commercially reasonable precautions to keep all information obtained from our online visitors secure against unauthorized access and use and we periodically review our security measures. 

### Links to Other Sites

Our site contains links to other web sites. These sites are not covered by this privacy statement, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other sites. 

### Changes

By using our site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site, and your continued use constitutes acceptance of those changes. Thank you for visiting our site, and for taking the time to read this policy. 

|  |
